<resources>

    <string name="accServiceDesc">⛵ This service allows compatible applications to easily counteract small device movements within their user interface.\n\n🏝️ This can improve screen readability and possibly alleviate motion sickness while on the go, e.g. while reading in a moving vehicle.\n\n🛡️ The app needs your permission to know which window is visible on the screen. It does not read window contents.\n\nℹ️ Find more info, implementation details and examples on:\n\ngithub.com/Sublimis/SteadyScreen</string>
    <string name="appDesc">⛵ This service allows compatible applications to easily counteract small device movements within their user interface.\n\n🏝️ This can improve screen readability and possibly alleviate motion sickness while on the go, e.g. while reading in a moving vehicle.\n\n⚡ The application has been crafted very meticulously, in order to minimize resource usage and maximize performance.\n\nHope you enjoy it 😊</string>
    <string name="aboutScreenTranslationsTitle">Translations</string>
    <string name="aboutScreenTranslationsText">Help translate this app and get a free license! More info: </string>
    <string name="aboutScreenLicenseTitle">App license</string>
    <string name="aboutScreenLicenseText">This application is free and works without limitations. However, the parameters will return to their default values after 1 hour without a license.</string>
    <string name="aboutScreenGithubLink">Stilly on GitHub</string>
    <string name="openSourceLicensesTitle">Open source licenses</string>

    <string name="loremIpsum">(This text is for demonstration purposes)\n\nThe soldier with the green whiskers led them through the streets of the Emerald City until they reached the room where the Guardian of the Gates lived. This officer unlocked their spectacles to put them back in his great box, and then he politely opened the gate for our friends.\n\n\"Which road leads to the Wicked Witch of the West?\" asked Dorothy.\n\n\"There is no road,\" answered the Guardian of the Gates. \"No one ever wishes to go that way.\"\n\n\"How, then, are we to find her?\" inquired the girl.\n\n\"That will be easy,\" replied the man, \"for when she knows you are in the country of the Winkies she will find you, and make you all her slaves.\"\n\n\"Perhaps not,\" said the Scarecrow, \"for we mean to destroy her.\"\n\n\"Oh, that is different,\" said the Guardian of the Gates. \"No one has ever destroyed her before, so I naturally thought she would make slaves of you, as she has of the rest. But take care; for she is wicked and fierce, and may not allow you to destroy her. Keep to the West, where the sun sets, and you cannot fail to find her.\"\n\nThey thanked him and bade him good-bye, and turned toward the West, walking over fields of soft grass dotted here and there with daisies and buttercups. Dorothy still wore the pretty silk dress she had put on in the palace, but now, to her surprise, she found it was no longer green, but pure white. The ribbon around Toto\'s neck had also lost its green color and was as white as Dorothy\'s dress.\n\nThe Emerald City was soon left far behind. As they advanced the ground became rougher and hillier, for there were no farms nor houses in this country of the West, and the ground was untilled.\n\nIn the afternoon the sun shone hot in their faces, for there were no trees to offer them shade; so that before night Dorothy and Toto and the Lion were tired, and lay down upon the grass and fell asleep, with the Woodman and the Scarecrow keeping watch.\n\nNow the Wicked Witch of the West had but one eye, yet that was as powerful as a telescope, and could see everywhere. So, as she sat in the door of her castle, she happened to look around and saw Dorothy lying asleep, with her friends all about her. They were a long distance off, but the Wicked Witch was angry to find them in her country; so she blew upon a silver whistle that hung around her neck.\n\nAt once there came running to her from all directions a pack of great wolves. They had long legs and fierce eyes and sharp teeth.\n\n\"Go to those people,\" said the Witch, \"and tear them to pieces.\"\n\n\"Are you not going to make them your slaves?\" asked the leader of the wolves.\n\n\"No,\" she answered, \"one is of tin, and one of straw; one is a girl and another a Lion. None of them is fit to work, so you may tear them into small pieces.\"\n\n\"Very well,\" said the wolf, and he dashed away at full speed, followed by the others.\n\nIt was lucky the Scarecrow and the Woodman were wide awake and heard the wolves coming.\n\n\"This is my fight,\" said the Woodman, \"so get behind me and I will meet them as they come.\"\n\nHe seized his axe, which he had made very sharp, and as the leader of the wolves came on the Tin Woodman swung his arm and chopped the wolf\'s head from its body, so that it immediately died. As soon as he could raise his axe another wolf came up, and he also fell under the sharp edge of the Tin Woodman\'s weapon. There were forty wolves, and forty times a wolf was killed, so that at last they all lay dead in a heap before the Woodman.\n\nThen he put down his axe and sat beside the Scarecrow, who said, \"It was a good fight, friend.\"\n\nThey waited until Dorothy awoke the next morning. The little girl was quite frightened when she saw the great pile of shaggy wolves, but the Tin Woodman told her all. She thanked him for saving them and sat down to breakfast, after which they started again upon their journey.\n\nNow this same morning the Wicked Witch came to the door of her castle and looked out with her one eye that could see far off. She saw all her wolves lying dead, and the strangers still traveling through her country. This made her angrier than before, and she blew her silver whistle twice.\n\nStraightway a great flock of wild crows came flying toward her, enough to darken the sky.\n\nAnd the Wicked Witch said to the King Crow, \"Fly at once to the strangers; peck out their eyes and tear them to pieces.\"\n\nThe wild crows flew in one great flock toward Dorothy and her companions. When the little girl saw them coming she was afraid.\n\nBut the Scarecrow said, \"This is my battle, so lie down beside me and you will not be harmed.\"\n\nSo they all lay upon the ground except the Scarecrow, and he stood up and stretched out his arms. And when the crows saw him they were frightened, as these birds always are by scarecrows, and did not dare to come any nearer. But the King Crow said:\n\n\"It is only a stuffed man. I will peck his eyes out.\"\n\nThe King Crow flew at the Scarecrow, who caught it by the head and twisted its neck until it died. And then another crow flew at him, and the Scarecrow twisted its neck also. There were forty crows, and forty times the Scarecrow twisted a neck, until at last all were lying dead beside him. Then he called to his companions to rise, and again they went upon their journey.\n\nWhen the Wicked Witch looked out again and saw all her crows lying in a heap, she got into a terrible rage, and blew three times upon her silver whistle.\n\nForthwith there was heard a great buzzing in the air, and a swarm of black bees came flying toward her.\n\n\"Go to the strangers and sting them to death!\" commanded the Witch, and the bees turned and flew rapidly until they came to where Dorothy and her friends were walking. But the Woodman had seen them coming, and the Scarecrow had decided what to do.\n\n\"Take out my straw and scatter it over the little girl and the dog and the Lion,\" he said to the Woodman, \"and the bees cannot sting them.\" This the Woodman did, and as Dorothy lay close beside the Lion and held Toto in her arms, the straw covered them entirely.\n\nThe bees came and found no one but the Woodman to sting, so they flew at him and broke off all their stings against the tin, without hurting the Woodman at all. And as bees cannot live when their stings are broken that was the end of the black bees, and they lay scattered thick about the Woodman, like little heaps of fine coal.\n\nThen Dorothy and the Lion got up, and the girl helped the Tin Woodman put the straw back into the Scarecrow again, until he was as good as ever. So they started upon their journey once more.\n\nThe Wicked Witch was so angry when she saw her black bees in little heaps like fine coal that she stamped her foot and tore her hair and gnashed her teeth. And then she called a dozen of her slaves, who were the Winkies, and gave them sharp spears, telling them to go to the strangers and destroy them.\n\nThe Winkies were not a brave people, but they had to do as they were told. So they marched away until they came near to Dorothy. Then the Lion gave a great roar and sprang towards them, and the poor Winkies were so frightened that they ran back as fast as they could.\n\nWhen they returned to the castle the Wicked Witch beat them well with a strap, and sent them back to their work, after which she sat down to think what she should do next. She could not understand how all her plans to destroy these strangers had failed; but she was a powerful Witch, as well as a wicked one, and she soon made up her mind how to act.\n\nThere was, in her cupboard, a Golden Cap, with a circle of diamonds and rubies running round it. This Golden Cap had a charm. Whoever owned it could call three times upon the Winged Monkeys, who would obey any order they were given. But no person could command these strange creatures more than three times. Twice already the Wicked Witch had used the charm of the Cap. Once was when she had made the Winkies her slaves, and set herself to rule over their country. The Winged Monkeys had helped her do this. The second time was when she had fought against the Great Oz himself, and driven him out of the land of the West. The Winged Monkeys had also helped her in doing this. Only once more could she use this Golden Cap, for which reason she did not like to do so until all her other powers were exhausted. But now that her fierce wolves and her wild crows and her stinging bees were gone, and her slaves had been scared away by the Cowardly Lion, she saw there was only one way left to destroy Dorothy and her friends.\n\nSo the Wicked Witch took the Golden Cap from her cupboard and placed it upon her head. Then she stood upon her left foot and said slowly:\n\n\"Ep-pe, pep-pe, kak-ke!\"\n\nNext she stood upon her right foot and said:\n\n\"Hil-lo, hol-lo, hel-lo!\"\n\nAfter this she stood upon both feet and cried in a loud voice:\n\n\"Ziz-zy, zuz-zy, zik!\"\n\nNow the charm began to work. The sky was darkened, and a low rumbling sound was heard in the air. There was a rushing of many wings, a great chattering and laughing, and the sun came out of the dark sky to show the Wicked Witch surrounded by a crowd of monkeys, each with a pair of immense and powerful wings on his shoulders.</string>

    <string name="dialogConsentTitle">Consent</string>
    <string name="dialogConsentMessage">This application needs the AccessibilityService API to retrieve interactive windows on the screen, in order to find compatible ones.\n\nThe service then sends multiple \"move window\" accessibility actions to such windows, as needed, to perform the intended function.</string>
    <string name="dialogConsentButton">Accept</string>

    <string name="dialogInfoTitle" translatable="false">@string/menuInfo</string>
    <string name="dialogInfoMessage">Shake the device a little. Notice how the background content softens these movements, making on-screen reading easier. (Stilly service must be enabled in the Accessibility settings for this to happen.)\n\nThis functionality can be easily implemented in any application. Please follow the instructions on GitHub.</string>
    <string name="dialogInfoButton">Go to GitHub</string>

    <string name="dialogRestoreDefaultsTitle" translatable="false">@string/menuRestoreDefaults</string>
    <string name="dialogRestoreDefaultsMessage">Restore settings to default values?</string>

    <string name="serviceInactiveText">Service is disabled, click here to enable.</string>

    <string name="menuTheme">Theme</string>
    <string name="menuIncreaseTextSize">Increase text size</string>
    <string name="menuDecreaseTextSize">Decrease text size</string>
    <string name="menuInfo">Info</string>
    <string name="menuSettings">Accessibility settings</string>
    <string name="menuRestoreDefaults">Restore defaults</string>
    <string name="menuAbout">About</string>
    <string name="menuLicense">Upgrade your license</string>
    <string name="menuRateAndComment">Rate us</string>
    <string name="menuSendDebugFeedback">Report an issue</string>

    <string name="paramSensorRate">Sensor rate</string>
    <string name="paramDamping">Damping</string>
    <string name="paramRecoil">Recoil</string>
    <string name="paramLinearScaling">Linear scaling</string>
    <string name="paramForceScaling">Force scaling</string>

    <string name="paramSensorRateInfo">This sets the desired sensor rate. Higher values may consume more battery. This may differ from the measured sensor rate as the system ultimately decides which rate to provide.</string>
    <string name="paramDampingInfo">Increasing this will slow down and attenuate movements, making them less sensitive to larger forces.</string>
    <string name="paramRecoilInfo">Increasing this will reduce sensitivity to small oscillations and make movements less sensitive to larger forces.</string>
    <string name="paramLinearScalingInfo">This scales the movements linearly, making them larger or smaller without affecting the calculations.</string>
    <string name="paramForceScalingInfo">This scales the forces before calculations, which in turn affects the overall magnitude of movements.</string>
    <string name="measuredSensorRateInfo">Current sensor rate as measured by the app. This may differ from the desired sensor rate as the system ultimately decides which rate to provide.</string>

    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>

    <string name="measuredSensorRate">Measured sensor rate</string>
    <string name="ratePerSecond">%1$s Hz</string>

    <string name="dialogReviewNudgeMessage">Are you enjoying this app?</string>
    <string name="dialogReviewNudgeMessage2">Thanks! Please write a nice review or rate us 5 stars on the Play Store.</string>
    <string name="dialogButtonRateOnPlayStore">Rate on Play Store</string>

    <string name="generalError">Some error occurred. Please try again.</string>

    <string name="ultimateLicenseTitle">Ultimate License</string>
    <string name="licenseItemAlreadyOwned">License item already owned</string>

    <string name="licenseSuccessDialogTitle" translatable="false">@string/app_name</string>
    <string name="licenseSuccessDialogMessage">The app was licensed successfully. Thank you for your support!</string>

    <string name="ultimateLicenseLabel">Ultimate</string>

</resources>
